I have a story for the
Spanish speakers.
I wanted this meditation, this
migration poster, clamp knowledge to
this often. I never teach the whole thing; it would be
two or three parts, and then
we're done. I'll try, especially
cool Latin American group, whether
we do the whole poster today.
We did it once in my whole life,
1998. I have the
whole thing translated.
I'll give you a
translation of it tonight. The first thing I'll talk about is
the explanation to the bands.
Then I'll talk about each individual
bee with horse racing. Allah
tries to speak quickly.
We try to accomplish something like a big
thing in a short amount of time.
We have a time limit. It has
39. I can do that.
Medium horse racing.
I have, I have given the numbers for this
year.
I can't see that very well, and it
's a small 12.
They weren't there. I wrote you down. I
tried to make it look like
woodcuts again. I don't know
the ethical and see, but I did
n't want to destroy the feeling of guilt.
First teacher of the current one, the
lama.  who wrote the famous long book
that we learn in this law,
spend 25 years with this book,
because now I think 21
Polycom neighbors are better, it's also the
heart chamber of my teacher,
I believe he is the greatest
writer in the history of
[music],
perhaps the last great, the last
great political book ever written,
this is written purely in Tibetan,
and that's already all
the special characteristics of the coming
from meditation.
I can't list all the advantages of
innovations,
I can tell you that every, actually
every, spiritual practice that gives the trainer the
pure ability to
have a very concentrated performance,
14 much, much higher,
leaves a stronger chamber, stronger chamber, these
are the directions
now, talking about the ability to
concentrate, says everything that is found through the
[music]
conditions that help, good
[music],
the eight,
he demands time, learned this morning,
5 problem solutions that the Russians
report from Jürgen Klopp, they have,
the Russian speakers, we
know where these five problems, how you find the
middle way of the two  Extremes
can distinguish
this object loses something don't do
when the room goes off let's sleep until
tomorrow 40 dollars
it's not broken is trying
not to fix it
well goes tried not to check it
if he doesn't just take the battery out of the room
well in it will be for himself that a
shot that someone a massage I've
heard that myself and what happens with yoga
then with yoga it has
n't happened personally yet it starts off well too
many reports about the way
back to the guests through that in the job
through would not repeat
how many there are nine states of mind through which you
go through Villa Medici is
you have learned the desire of a long time
this morning in the early morning they
sleep then something that we don't where
we haven't spoken the
six
[music]
then he speaks the book the essence of the
middle way master the elephant
of the guests who all found wants to go in the
wrong direction because hitting the ground
says remembrance of the number is the
subject of a meditation
withdrawing something of the mind back then
you need the Hesse take the hook take
the pen that's why you have back in
the  Elephant text here a very
sensitive place in the ear and so a
small person elephant to go
where he is supposed to go says use
the iron axe of his wisdom
I want I will this elephant
from this famous book in India at
four donations for this picture that I am
making here
[Music]
I will we will now everything in the
poster white pattern drawn is about that
later so I will
not repeat that now
then he ends with a poem and the
sponsor who paid for the wood karin
he will give me the karma pour the father of
this person who died
67 completed it is produced in a
refugee camp 99%
died
[Music]
[Music] do
you like I am very hot and you try
to find help
the woodcut is very clear that took
many hours to
figure out but I figured it out
that the tip of that
this perfect meditation to think
not so thinks not to afternoon
mind on the different
not that I that means bringing back the mind
cacau r brings back the games  to the
object in the left hand
[Music]
they are others holding elephants he has them there is
a spirit on the
meditation path now uses that his
two tools black and white is that
you believe
[Music]
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
The Hague
gesture begins her voting behavior to
speak that is the task of the 420
dollars holding the hand on
why brings him back
30 dollars answer another 20
[Music]
to the whole
six of the meditation is not
appropriate here because every curve 30 spectators
force help
[Music]
beginning of the street counts what happens
here
while you speak also meditation
[Music]
only begin to shed
above become the whole head is not
enough had not spoken
distraction is very strong are in the other
object now that is a technically
spoken
[Music]
distraction actually to go to an analogy
act up there because the head of the
apparently is not in yoga he
killed
you were a nice person
[Music]
of 7 something like that certainly not as the last
time again spaghetti now laid out on the floor I have
spilled
[Music]
seeing the fire gets smaller
if you continue to come up meditation
in meditation status number 8
$420 question how much effort must I
make in meditation to reach status
number eight I think that's right,
maybe
[Music]
somehow to get there and you are not
deep meditation
I hope if he only reached nine
we that helps you to calculate the second of the new
meditation levels
[Music]
great to think you get to
repeat
[Music]
in the picture number eight a little green not
meditate sleep
[Music]
the Jewish elephant has no
tiredness
[Music]
it is very difficult for meditation
study is simply to run into the booth, get out of it, it
works again I can't show
his own money but that's
right, try it out,
you have to find where you're going to have
real fun
[Music] do
n't be afraid they understand that anyway
[Music]
sometimes everything breaks for me,
what means means in meditation
when I say  Investment is clear,
which doesn't mean the object is very
clear. It had to be a question to
understand a little better what we clearly understand
during such
corruption risks. Now,
the clear subject of 50 dollars doesn't mean
the quality of communication. A 110
study of meditation means
clarity. Things are clear.
I have that I
can see the color of the eyes and look back in the afternoon.
[Music]
Went
to China is fun. To be
able to go to conferences, we go too much. My children
all talk.
[Music]
The boy says the girl.
A little tension between the
boys. The girl locked up.
[Music]
And they lived, and the lip starts to go like this.
The faces of the spectators in the cinema at
the moment you look at the book. I can see them
here. I already have them all. So that's
clear, that clarity.
[Laughter]
The film is good meditation and
happily excited
at the moment of the film.
[Music]
That's, we haven't
finished yet. Now, the connection is
Mr. Appel. Is Mr. How much is
the head of  The installation
of larger ones is fully mobile
[Music]
the wealth of this size remains,
what will be less
[Music]
[Applause]
with one's own money
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] [Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
[Applause] [Music] [Applause]
big enough for 3
[Music] [Music] [Music
] [Applause] [Music] [Applause]
that's what the 10,000 university in Israel
[Music] such a
size finished but there is
war between Israel and Palestine
[Music]
people come together
[Applause]
all the booths I don't want to
mention donations then not to say that
she has to leave early tomorrow morning to
help nuns with this Britta
I believe this will help to have peace in the
Middle East
accordingly
we need millions of dollars
they only need five million dollars
[Music]
now that there are many yes it
translated into Hebrew because now a
group of students in this  The center
has started a big project,
the whole thing translated into Arabic. There are
billions of jobs that have been done so far, as expected back then. Thank you very much.
[Applause]
She had many obstacles.
It wasn't easy going from one student to
many hundreds of students. It is
now the largest political
group. It's not always easy, but that has to be
disrupted.
[Music] [
Music] Targets become
[Music]
Distractions to noises. The first
taste of taste, these are the
objects distracted.
[Music]
This brings money again now, comes back to
work.
[Music] [
Music]
Number 3 degrees back and bridges the gap
between Neuerburg.
They are hate. He has a black
color. He rides the elephant in
Hartmann's. No sense that during
meditation and to dream, the body is
perfect. Everyone wants to take the
chance so good in meditation. But
actually, you don't think about anything
when you say you have great pressure,
but this one is nothing to think about.
It is very, very dangerous.
It feels as if you are meditating.
He has the hard ruler.  added that
is day of silence bracket
[Music]
now the man of the monkeys in front of the
elephant
that is back cooperation turned is
probably something with the Anatoli without any
input from capturing away is and you
are in a position to bring the case back
remembers what should have done
his head has finally become a clue
the black abbot busy
guests
now it turns back and aims
at meditation
maybe I should go back to meditation for
this stands the number 16
yes you had you have just at home
is the property good but I don't let go that one immediately
in a
future afternoon hangs themselves they
are get I stay true to myself we all
with all our strength but it doesn't feel it doesn't feel
happy desire but
you do that is number 16 that's where
the numbers come in old
writings one quickly a small
tent
17 what happens until 17
she is means the space is is
extraordinarily well developed
[Music]
you no longer have a problem
losing the object we think the other way
we have fun is a
fruit of his  hand outstretched similarly
to
the wheel of life which speaks
has a different meaning left
here for
three days I am diamond
business is the safest group in the
whole world was left in the other ring
can put the people in it
people want me to become good
people but they are already
better
it is nice though your problem is not
that bad things will happen they do
bad things we will
not stand anyone's ring
your problem is you have so many good
things you want to do you don't know
which one is important right that
is so we try everything ourselves
almost not just to make good money
makes the projects you are doing now
good
the priority of our good actions
to find out how good the action is more
important than the other routes driving
was halfway through the tenants through the
development of meditation now to
a back to try to
achieve a second goal during the same situation
[Music]
then switch after the halfway and
stand there then she is no longer solely
focused if you tell me
[Music]
the world is off everything good
try everything needle with the needle with two
points you can't do anything  Seeing
this means that a meditation, another,
I focus halfway, even it looks good,
everything you do
in the announcement, the parents, people have
brought
[Music]
because the hand stretches out, 20
[Music], the body's
traction, almost no distraction anymore,
which animal has now become white, so the monkey has
now become white, and
not exert much anymore because the
flame is now small,
you don't have to exert yourself so much anymore,
meditation, and number 20 is
a new idea that I haven't taught you yet, it's
called
[Music]
because your meditation takes a while,
feels a bit depressing and
feels heavy, then forget the
story with the films, that's a
bad film, what can we do
inside to raise the mind, and then say
we are then at some point, the one he loves,
ever in which you love, then
automatically the mind but also your attitude will
change, and that is,
so to speak, from within, you
then raise the mind, then you think like your
parents who loved you very much
[Music],
that is the antidote if you
feel somewhat heavy in meditation
[Music]
Here I want to change something.
Wait, someone please tell me
what happens in mental stage number five. Because
I don't know myself. In
this stage, there's no more significant
drowsiness. So here in this
monastery,
it's in stage 21, so no more drowsiness.
Then you're actually supposed to be that
the elephant is completely white, but, but, but there's still
a bit of
subtle drowsiness. When you look like
half of it, so the
drowsiness is gone, but that you're completely
gone, like, that has
n't happened yet. That I can't completely get rid of it. In stage
22, the spirit is now completely
peaceful. Station in the castle, and in the
text it says in quotation marks, "
no great danger anymore of becoming
drowsy." So there's still a
small chance that you'll sleep. So it's
not a big problem now, but
between you and me, there's another small problem.
[Music]
Now, stage 23, that means that you are
ready to work very hard on your
meditation.
[Music]
You are ready to work so hard
that it becomes perfect. Often, it has to be
seen that way.  The obstacles
get smaller and smaller,
then you need even more effort
to really...
It's not that much effort
to fight the obvious, the obvious laziness, but afterwards, when there
's still so much... then you need
much more tension. The last
ten percent of spiritual
progress requires much more
effort, but I do
n't really see what looks like
effort there.
[Music]
The mind has become completely calm,
and you can see here that the explanation has
become longer. So not even with
so much drowsiness, what was that about?
And no more busy mind for 20
dollars,
a subtle one, no more subtle busy
mind. What is that? She needs money
to come.
If Luca helps her, it's 10 and 10 become...
that I think of Japan, that's right, that's
the water under the ice. So at 24, so far
the atheist knows...
[Music]
We have now, so
we have laid down this busy leader, even the
subtle busy one. Even if it
only comes for a second, that you are
concerned with what he lets others do,
then it only works like this
currently.  Is your meditation so
powerful? This is the seventh of the
new meditations
[Music]
even if you feel that he
will soon almost think about what she has to do
and again 25
[Music]
he will make the explanation quite long.
It is really so difficult
to make a nun, but a nun, that took five
hours,
maybe that's why they now
keep their vows and those who don't keep them are left behind,
and you now begin to
get the only concentration and the meditation is
automatic after he only
needed a few minutes at the beginning, and
number 27, here too, the curve, the
picture about number 23,
that needs, so to speak, exchange your
brand new mat for an old one, that he
has all that, that's a super alto math,
I give, he is a good friend of
his meditation cushion,
he has a very good, strong, strong
habit, doesn't need a hook anymore,
if we are not broken, then do
n't repair it, doesn't need one or two
tools anymore,
you shouldn't use them too much,
that is 28
and that should actually be the best,
the cost level  That's
actually how it is, we have to be finished now,
but now we still have to go to
Father.
[Music]
So he's now controlling his mind,
expecting on his mind, that's the
preparatory step at the first
form, rich level, perfection, and now
you can see the teachers directly
because the meditation is perfect enough,
the body feels incredible, it feels
like a cotton ball, you
have the feeling you're flying in the air.
If you're out of the snug for an hour,
then you have the feeling you're getting... She taught
us how to
correct ourselves in the present moment, and she's a
great yoga master. I saw her in
Thailand, and then you go to her like that,
and then
when you put her in a headstand,
it's like she's putting on ice cream.
[Music]
Then she also makes such
noises, and you have the feeling you're
flying. The physical body in a
charming way feels fantastic, like you're
flying. High feeling 31, the
mental high.
When her father comes, then there are
extreme physical and mental
feelings of happiness and...  32 and here come the
stockbrokers and pharma, collecting for this, which
means you see the majority directly,
then you can cut the wheel of life,
and at the root, be
link number one at link number one,
this fire, you cut through it heavily, what
is even better than that?
This will now be, so to speak, a way of
life, because the direct
view of the apprenticeship begins
to influence your life,
normal life back, since then
you will immediately remember, it already begins with the fact
that you no longer write to your children,
the pen enormously, mind, it's
perfect, and that is after the very
direct majority, we save them in the
majority, and then you will
capitulate, get used to it, what and when do
you achieve the third group victory at
your festival, in meditation achieved
third place, the path of going,
all the small boundaries between this path
are only reachable on the cushion,
you cannot go from Barschel straight ahead,
driver gave gas where it is so
harder, there is always a meditation
in between, otherwise he doesn't get from one
path to the other, meditations are,
so to speak, like the rungs of a ladder  The
last fire, that's still an
effort, the fourth way, that's the way
of habituation, get used to what
you saw when he saw the teaching, saw it
directly,
now you've already said I have
n't emptied this whole
poster for 25 years, and what is your job now,
now you have to teach it to others correctly,
and I will give you
the correct translation
of the whole thing in the next few days, so it comes already
finished, he didn't properly
describe what happens at each of the nine
levels, so to speak,
in brackets so that you can see that it's
not there, his teacher is de  n mind
control then we don't know
exactly says that is and that he
taught himself the other homework
then say what is the meaning
of the new names
[Music]
the st
super
[Music]